(Leonard:)Sheldon,
(Amy:)I want you to take
that cap off.
(Sheldon:)That nagging tone is
helping my anxiety, yeah.
(Sheldon:)But if you could maybe just go
ten percent less shrill,
(Sheldon:)that'd really put the zip-a-dee
in my doo-dah.
(Amy:)I'm sorry, but
you know we agreed
(Amy:)not to bring work
to date night.
(Sheldon:)There you go, perfect.
(Amy:)Sheldon, stop it,
I'm not kidding.
(Amy:)Take the cap off, and
put the notebook away.
(Sheldon:)But after months of struggling,
I'm finally making progress.
(Amy:)You don't need to drive yourself
crazy in order to be productive.
(Sheldon:)Or do I, hmm?
(Sheldon:)Sir Isaac Newton wrote
his Principia
(Sheldon:)while convinced he was
an armadillo.
(Amy:)That's not true.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, maybe it is,
maybe it isn't.
(Sheldon:)I have been
hallucinating lately.
(Amy:)Sheldon, this has to stop.
(Amy:)You need to get some sleep
and take care of yourself.
(Sheldon:)Amy, I have gotten more done
in the last few days
(Sheldon:)than I have since I made
the switch to dark matter.
(Sheldon:)What if I stop doing this,
and it all goes away?